dealocx.com 2016-11-04

# Dealocx - Privacy Policy

We at Dealocx Media Private Limited (the “Company”, “we”, or “us”) are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our customers. This Privacy Policy entails the way in which your personal information will be collected, used, shared, stored, protected or disclosed by us when you use our Services. This Privacy Policy applies to the Software Application, DEALOCX and the Program (the “Application” or “Services”) developed by us which helps customers search and discover outlets within the DEALOCX Network, shop and earn DEALOCX chips which can be further redeemed at any Supplier within the DEALOCX Network. By using our Services, You agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. If you do not accept the terms of this Privacy Policy and Terms of Service, you are directed to discontinue accessing/using our Application in any way. We strongly recommend that you read the policy carefully before proceeding with any transaction on our Application. All references to any capitalized word not defined under this Policy shall be construed as references to the Terms of Service. 

1\. What information we collect?

(a) Personal Information

When you install the Application on your device, we collect your Personal Information for registration including but not limited to your phone number, name, email id, date of birth, gender, profile picture, call log, friend list from Facebook and Google+, bill photos, bill details, pictures of shops or establishments, menu pictures, Facebook, Google+, Twitter Account page URLs and details of the transaction being carried on the DEALOCX portal. Please note that this information is knowingly provided by you and we receive and store this information with us for data statistics, user support and enhanced usage of our Services.

(b) Other Information

We may also follow you on Facebook, Twitter, or any other social networking website where you have an account and collect information about you as available to the general public on these social networking websites. Additionally, with your permission/consent, we may also collect photos, reviews or feedbacks uploaded/shared by you on Facebook or any other social networking website.

(c) Usage Information

When you install or use our Services we collect and store information about your computer or mobile device. Some of the information we collect includes your computer IP addresses, mobile device ids (the unique identifier assigned to a device by a manufacturer), technical information about your computer or mobile device (such as type of device, web browser or operating system), your mobile device’s geographic location (specific geographic location if you’ve enabled collection of that information, or general geographic location automatically) and “cookie” information of the page you requested. “Cookies” are identifiers we transfer to your computer or mobile device that allow us to recognize your browser or mobile device and tell us how and when the pages and features in our Services are visited and by how many people. You may be able to change the preferences on your browser or mobile device to prevent or limit your computer or device’s acceptance of cookies, but this may prevent you from taking advantage of some of our features. If you click on a link to a third party website, such third party may also transmit cookies to you. You hereby agree that this Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

2\. Why we collect your information?

We collect information about you for the following general purposes:   
**(a)** For registration and to manage your account, including to facilitate your access to and use of our Services;   
**(b)** To communicate with you in general, including to provide information about us;   
**(c)** To respond to your questions and comments,   
**(d)** To notify you about special offers that may be of interest to you;   
**(e)** To prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and to enforce our Terms of Use.

3\. With whom we share your information?

We neither rent nor sell your Personal and/or Other Information to anyone. However, we do share your Personal and/or Other Information with third parties as described below:

**• DEALOCX Partners :** To the extent you have carried out the sale and purchase of any product at the online or offline counter of any DEALOCX Partner or participated in any other activity sponsored or offered through the Application on behalf of the DEALOCX Partner, we may provide such DEALOCX Partners with your Personal and/or Other Information (a) in order for the DEALOCX Partner to validate your transaction so as to help you earn points (b) to combat fraud, (c) to facilitate a direct relationship between the DEALOCX Partner and you or (d) to enable the DEALOCX Partner to communicate electronically with you with respect to Schemes & Offers related to such DEALOCX Partner. 

**• Suppliers :** To the extent you redeem your points at any of the Suppliers within the DEALOCX Network or participate in any other activity sponsored or offered through the Application on behalf of the Supplier, we may provide such Suppliers with your Personal and/or Other Information (a) in order for the Supplier to assist Redemption of points against the DEALOCX Chips (b) to combat fraud, (c) to facilitate a direct relationship between the Supplier and you or (d) to enable the Supplier to communicate electronically with you with respect to Schemes & Offers related to such Supplier. 

**• Third-party vendors :** We employ third party vendors to provide Services on our behalf for varied purposes like business analytics, customer service, marketing, distribution etc. We may authorize such vendors to collect information on our behalf in order to operate features of our Application or to deliver services tailored to your needs. We assure that such information used by third party vendors is only to perform their functions and they are not permitted to share or use that information for any other purpose.

**• Companies within our corporate family :** We may be required to provide information about you to our parent or subsidiary company or corporate affiliates. To the extent our parent company or subsidiaries or corporate affiliates have information about you, they will follow the best practices as described in this Privacy Policy. 

**• Affiliated Websites :** If you were referred to us from another website, we may have to share information pertaining to registration information including but not limited to name, e-mail address, phone numbers, gender, date of birth etc. In such instances we encourage you to read and review their Privacy Policy of the website that referred you to us. We will not be responsible for the handling of such information by them.

**• Business Transfers :** We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that would be transferred. Also, if we (or our assets) are acquired, or if we go out of business, enter bankruptcy, or go through some other change of control, Personal and Other Information would be one of the assets transferred to or acquired by a third party.

**• Government Bodies :** We may disclose your Personal Information and Usage Information as and when required in response to a sub-poena, court order, government demand or to comply with any legal requirements for protecting our interest. We will contact you by e-mail when we have to adhere to such legal request. All communications sent by us at such email address shall be deemed to have been communicated to you. 

4\. How do we protect your information?

We want you to have full faith in having your information safe and secure with us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the Personal Information, Other Information and Usage Information submitted to us. While no Services can guarantee full-proof security, we have appropriate administrative, technical and security procedures to keep your information intact, secure and confidential. Your information is handled only for the purposes required by authorized employees or agents or third party vendors and the like and we employ appropriate firewalls, encryption technologies and intrusion detection systems to keep your information secure and safe from any unauthorized use. 

5\. How can I change my information and what happens when I cancel my account?

You can anytime ask us to amend the information provided by you by contacting us at [support@dealocx.com](mailto:support@dealocx.com). We will make changes to the information provided by you as soon as reasonably practicable. If you wish to cancel your account you should contact us at support@dealocx.com. However, you should take note that if even after the suspension of your account we will retain your Personal Information and Usage Information for complying with certain regulatory or legal obligations, resolving disputes, preventing fraud, enforcing agreements or for any other business reasons.

6\. What about the safety of children?

Our Services are directed to serve a very general audience. We reserve a right of use of our Services to persons above 18 years of age. We do not knowingly collect Personal and Other Information from anyone under the age of 18. If we discover that a person below 18 years of age or younger has provided Personal and Other Information to us, we automatically delete such information. If you are a parent or guardian of a minor under the age of 18 years and believe he or she has disclosed Personal Information to us, please contact us at [support@dealocx.com](mailto:support@dealocx.com).

7\. How does a change in our Privacy Policy affect you?

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes in the way we use your Personal, Other or Usage Information, we will notify you (for example, by email or a sign-in notification or some other means). By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you are agreeing to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy; if you do not agree to the change, simply don’t use the Service after the change is effective, in which case the change will not apply to you.

8\. How can you contact us?

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy please feel free to contact us at [support@dealocx.com](mailto:support@dealocx.com).
